Yes.
But even considering that swimrun is growing so much in Europe,
And there will be new races in Spain, Italy, Greece, it is one in California, Australia.
Then you do not want to run in a full suit.
So then we have produced this, and it is just like the race costume.
It is 6 mm floating panel on.
You can combine with a linen, if you would like to.
And not run with bare torso or sports bra, or what you have under.
Well, welcome.
Thanks, Per.
Dennis
Oh, sponsors and stuff.
Limited Edition as well.
We swam 25km in four days.
Then there were people from all over the world, and then it really was, all variants of equipment.
Wet suits, hats, some drove without every day.
It was 17 degrees in the water, so I thought it was too cold to swim without
But I was jealous of those who had like this.
Tank Top.
I thought it was too cold to drive completely without a swimsuit.
One day we got away late, African time ...
Then it was tide, and waves.
We chased buoy, the other kite surf.
What are they doing?
This is much more fun.